<resources>

    <string name="ticket_string">
    <![CDATA[
    Instead of printing off thousands of multi-page Convention programs and ordering the same number
    of paper tickets, we developed this app to conserve paper and allow you to have everything you
    need to know about Convention Weekend 2020 at your fingertips.
    <p>
    All Convention ticket holders received an email from our team with their digital ticket
    information. Android users can will use that email as their ticket into Convention. Please have
    the email up and ready for scanning at the door. Our team will be checking IDs at the door,
    those without IDs will be turned away. Purchased a ticket but didn\’t get an email? Contact us.
    <p>
    Ticket holders are encouraged to use the app as their event program for the weekend. A limited
    number of printed versions of the weekend program will be available upon request.
    ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="general_info_events_link"><a href="https://mockcon.com/documents/information.html">General Information</a></string>

    <string name="platform_rules_events_link"><a href="https://mockcon.com/documents/platformandrules.html">Platform and Rules</a></string>

    <string name="app_name">MockCon</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="about_string">
    <![CDATA[
    The Washington and Lee University Mock Convention is a simulated presidential nominating convention held every four years by the students of W&L.
    Its goal is to predict who the party out of power in the White House will nominate to run for President of the United States.
    <p>
    We got our start in 1908 when presidential candidate Williams Jennings Bryan announced a visit to Lexington, VA, sparking interest on W&L’s campus.
    The Forum, the campus’ largest political club at the time, hosted a replica of the upcoming Democratic Convention to honor the visit of Bryan and to
    heighten the excitement of the student body. The accurate prediction of Bryan as the nominee cemented Mock Convention as one of the core features of
    the Washington and Lee experience.
    <p>
    Over 100 years later, the students of Washington and Lee University have gathered to create one of the most ambitious, non-partisan student political
    research projects in the country. With the stage set for an intense contest for the 2020 Democratic nomination, we invite you to join us as, for the
    27th time, we celebrate the complexity and importance of the electoral process.
    ]]>

    </string>

    <string name="convention_chronicles_link"><a href="https://www.mockconvention.com/convention-chronicles">Convention Chronicles</a></string>

    <string name="newsroom_link"><a href="https://www.mockconvention.com/newsroom">Newsroom</a></string>

    <string name="team_name">MockCon</string>

    <string name="team_action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="team_string">
    <![CDATA[
    Washington and Lee Mock Convention is a nationally recognized and respected organization. Meet the students who are working hard to keep it that way.
    ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="mock_con_departments"><a href="https://www.mockconvention.com/our-team">Meet the MockCon Departments</a></string>



    <string name="memorabilia_name">MockCon</string>

    <string name="memorabilia_action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="memorabilia_string">
    <![CDATA[
    Our Memorabilia & Sales Team works hard to further the Mock Convention image beyond just politics. The team joins business and art to create and design exciting memorabilia to help
    the convention live beyond 2020. Explore our catalog below and take home a piece of Mock Con.
    ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="memorabilia_link"><a href="https://www.mockconvention.com/store">Visit the MockCon Store</a></string>



    <string name="convention_layout">For information regarding parking, the convention layout and seating, shuttles, safety and security, and more, please visit the following link: <a href="https://mockcon.com/documents/information.html">General Information</a></string>

    <string name="platform_rules_link">For information about the Mock Convention platform and rules, please visit the following link: <a href="https://mockcon.com/documents/platformandrules.html">Platform and Rules</a></string>


    <string name="contact_name">MockCon</string>

    <string name="contact_action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="contact_string">
    <![CDATA[
    Please contact Mock Convention below or via mockcon@mail.wlu.edu concerning any inquiries, comments, or suggestions - whether
    general or specific. We\'re excited to get in touch.
    ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="contact_link"><a href="https://www.mockconvention.com/contact">Contact the Convention Team</a></string>



    <string name="developer_contact_name">MockCon</string>

    <string name="developer_contact_action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="developer_contact_string">
    <![CDATA[
    Have a question about the app or want to give feedback on your experience? Contact our App Developer team via
    mockconappdevelopers@mail.wlu.edu.
    ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="developer_contact_link"><a href="https://mockcon.com/">Contact the App Developer Team</a></string>

    <string name="trevor_noah_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session Three</b>
        <p>
        <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        Trevor Noah is the host of the Emmy® and Peabody® Award-winning "The Daily Show" on Comedy
        Central.  The "Daily Show with Trevor Noah" recently received two 2019 Primetime Emmy
        nominations, including Outstanding Variety Talk Series and Outstanding Interactive Program.
        <p>
        Trevor has written, produced, and starred in 8 comedy specials, most recently including
        "Son of Patricia" on Netflix.  Trevor\'s success has also spanned to sold out shows over 5
        continents.  Trevor is currently crossing North America on his first ever arena outing with
        the "Loud & Clear Tour 2019."  In April 2019, Trevor launched his new podcast series "On
        Second Thought: The Trevor Noah Podcast" exclusively on Luminary.
        <p>
        Trevor Noah is the author of the #1 New York Times bestseller "Born a Crime: Stories from a
        South African Childhood" and its young readers adaptation "It\'s Trevor Noah: Born a Crime:
        Stories from a South African Childhood," which also debuted as a New York Times bestseller.
        The book received the Thurber Prize for American Humor and two NAACP Image Awards, one for
        Outstanding Literary Work by a Debut Author and another for Outstanding Literary Work in the
        Biography/Auto-Biography category.  The Audible edition of "Born a Crime," performed by Trevor,
        remains one of the top-selling, highest-rated, and most-commented-on Audible performances
        of all time.  To date, "Born a Crime" has sold over 1 million copies across all formats.
        <p>
        Trevor\'s production company, Day Zero Productions, recently partnered with Viacom and has
        several projects in development, including the feature film adaptation of Born a Crime
        starring Academy Award winner Lupita Nyong\'o, and a half-hour comedy with Roy Wood Jr. and
        Aaron McGruder at Comedy Central.
        <p>
        In April 2018, Noah launched the Trevor Noah Foundation, a youth development initiative that
        enhances youth preparedness for higher education or entry into the workforce.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="tara_mcgowan_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Politics & Media Panel</b>
        <p>
        <b>Location: Keller Theater - Lenfest</b>
        <p>
        Tara McGowan is the Founder and CEO of progressive group ACRONYM, which recently launched a
        $75 million digital effort to counter Trump online. A longtime Democratic strategist for
        groups like Priorities USA, NextGen, and the 2012 Obama campaign, Tara McGowan has quickly
        become the leading voice on digital politics on the Left. She\’s regularly featured in the
        New York Times, and other major print outlets, and she has spoken about the 2020 digital
        race for the White House with on NPR and CNN.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="symone_sanders_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session One</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        A champion for women, Symone D. Sanders is a strategist, communications consultant,
        CNN Political Commentator and served as a Spring 2018 Resident Fellow at Harvard’s Institute
        of Politics at the Kennedy School. Symone rose to prominence during her tenure as the
        National Press Secretary for U.S. Sen. Bernie Sanders 2016 presidential campaign. At 25,
        Symone demonstrated an uncanny command of the issues earning her a place in history as the
        youngest presidential press secretary on record and a spot on Rolling Stone Magazine\’s
        list of 16 young Americans shaping the 2016 election.
        <p>
        However, Symone was not new to presidential politics. When she was 16, she introduced former
        President Bill Clinton at a luncheon in Omaha, Nebraska. Following her remarks, President
        Clinton said, “Symone spoke so well I really hate to follow her.” President Clinton went on
        to write about Symone in his book, Giving: How Each of Us Can Change the World.
        <p>
        Now, Symone draws from her experience on the national stage to provide perceptive analysis
        on political and social issues. Her lively presentations challenge the conventional wisdom
        that strong communities are only defined by what we have in common. Instead, she outlines
        the way our differences contribute to effective social movements.
        <p>
        Symone has been featured on NPR, Fox News, MSNBC, NBC, BET, TV One and CNN. She has been
        profiled in the Washington Post, the New Yorker, ESSENCE Magazine and ELLE.  Symone now is
        Senior Advisor for Joe Biden\'s 2020 presidential campaign and currently Principal of the 360
        Group, LLC. where she provides strategic communications guidance to organizations, businesses,
        individuals, campaigns and candidates and helps clients find sound solutions to tough
        political and social problems. Symone has also been selected to serve as one of USC
        Dornsife\'s 2019 Fellows.

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="patti_solis_doyle_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session Two</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        Patti Solis Doyle is a nationally recognized political organizer, campaign strategist and
        CNN political commentator. She speaks regularly on the rise of women and minorities in
        politics, presidential campaigns and issues affecting Hispanic Americans.
        <p>
        She is president of Solis Strategies, a communications firm serving non-profits, NGOs and
        corporations.
        <p>
        Solis Doyle also co-founded Vendor Assistance Program, LLC (VAP), a Chicago-based financial
        services firm. VAP helps state governments finance and accelerate payments to their vendors,
        so those vendors can fund their operations, manage their cash flow, recognize revenue
        earlier, expand their businesses and create more local jobs. VAP recently raised $340 million
        for its program with the state of Illinois. Her work with VAP, governors and other state
        officials follows more than 20 years in politics, presidential campaigns and public service.
        She began her career working on Richard Daley\’s campaign for mayor of Chicago and later
        worked at Chicago City Hall. In 1991, she was among the first to join then-Governor Bill
        Clinton\’s presidential campaign. She served as a senior advisor to Hillary Clinton
        throughout that campaign and two terms in the White House. In 2000, Solis Doyle served as
        chief of staff to Clinton\’s first Senate campaign. She later managed Senator Clinton\’s
        political operations, PAC and 2006 re-election campaign. As campaign manager of Clinton\’s
        presidential bid (from January 2007 through February 2008), Solis Doyle was the first
        Hispanic woman to lead a presidential campaign.
        <p>
        During the 2008 general election, Solis Doyle joined the Obama for America campaign as chief
        of staff for vice presidential operations. In this role, she built a national team of policy,
        communications, political and field operatives in advance of the nominee\’s selection.
        She later managed day-to-day operations for vice presidential nominee Joe Biden. During the
        2012 presidential election, Solis Doyle served as an advisor to the Obama-Biden campaign.
        <p>
        In addition to her work with VAP, Solis Doyle works with Hispanic service organizations and
        student organizations across the U.S.
        <p>
        Hispanic magazine honored Solis Doyle with the Latinas of Excellence Award for her
        accomplishments in the area of government, politics and civil leadership. She also received
        the “Siempre Inspiran Award” from Siempre Mujer magazine, honoring remarkable Latinas whose
        achievements and contributions to their communities are helping shape the future of Hispanic
        women in this country. Hispanic Business magazine named her one of America\’s “100 Most
        Influential Hispanics.”
        <p>
        Solis Doyle received her Bachelor of Arts degree in communication from Northwestern
        University. She currently resides in Washington, DC, with her husband and two children.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="nadine_strossen_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session Two</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        Nadine Strossen, the John Marshall Harlan II Professor of Law at New York Law School, is a
        leading expert in constitutional law and human rights. She is the immediate past President
        of the American Civil Liberties Union (1991-2008), and now serves on the advisory boards of
        EPIC (the Electronic Privacy Information Center), FIRE (the Foundation for Individual Rights
        in Education), and Heterodox Academy. When Strossen stepped down as ACLU President, three
        ideologically diverse) Supreme Court Justices participated in her farewell/tribute luncheon:
        Ruth Bader Ginsburg, Antonin Scalia, and David Souter.
        <p>
        The National Law Journal has named Strossen one of America\’s “100 Most Influential Lawyers,”
        and several other publications have named her one of the country\’s most influential women.
        Her many honorary degrees and awards include the American Bar Association\’s prestigious
        Margaret Brent Women Lawyers of Achievement Award (2017).
        <p>
        Strossen has made thousands of public presentations before diverse audiences around the world,
        including on more than 500 campuses.  A frequent media commentator, she has published widely
        in both academic and general interest publications.  Her 2018 book, HATE:  Why We Should
        Resist it With Free Speech, Not Censorship, has earned praise from ideologically diverse
        experts, including progressive Harvard University Professor Cornel West and conservative
        Princeton University Professor Robert George. HATE was selected by Washington University
        (in St. Louis) as its 2019 “Common Read” for all incoming students.
        Her earlier book, Defending Pornography: Free Speech, Sex, and the Fight for Women\’s Rights,
        was named a New York Times “notable book” of 1995.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="mike_allen_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Politics & Media Panel</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Keller Theater - Lenfest</b>
        <p>
        Mike Allen is one of Washington\’s most influential and well-connected journalists. He is
        the co-founder and executive editor of Axios, a company delivering news and insights on
        politics, business, media, and tech. The company, whose name means “worthy” in Greek,
        specializes in high-quality news and analysis easily shared among the country\’s
        influential readers and across social platforms.
        <p>
        In addition to starting Axios, Allen was a co-founder at POLITICO, the digital media
        company that upended and revolutionized political and policy journalism in Washington, New
        York, and Europe. He not only reported on but also drove the day\’s conversations in and
        around the Beltway. His sharp journalistic experience and coveted insider status make him an
        ideal choice to discuss the latest political happenings. In presentations, he offers his
        non-partisan, energetic and up-to-the-minute insider perspective on the political issues of
        the day, the Trump administration, the Republican Congress, and building a business in an
        unsteady economy. Exclusively represented by Leading Authorities, Inc. speakers bureau, he
        has been praised for his dedication, passion, and unmatched ability to give a political story
        dimension and context.
        <p>
        Building A Political Powerhouse: In 2006, Allen joined POLITICO and sought to carve out a
        niche in the marketplace by focusing on giving readers one solid take-away from select stories.
        He served as the chief White House correspondent and was the founding father of the successful
        daily email tip-sheet Playbook. It quickly became the early-morning must read source for
        movers and shakers in politics and media. The New York Times called Allen “The Man the White
        House Wakes Up To,” and Vanity Fair said, “Reading Playbook is as close as you can come on a
        Washington morning to knowing everything.”
        <p> Award-Winning Political Coverage: TIME magazine named Allen one of its top 140 Twitter
        feeds, calling him “the Virgil of the beltway, leading the rest of us hapless Dantes through
        the inferno of America\’s political universe.” Vanity Fair named him to its 2011 (#39) and
        2012 (#19) “Top 50 New Establishment and Powers That Be” lists, and Allen also won the White
        House Correspondents’ Association\’s Merriman Smith Memorial Award for “Outstanding
        presidential coverage on deadline” in 2004.
        <p>
        Allen is also the creator of the daily newsletter, Morning Money, which gives readers insight
        into the intersection of Washington and Wall Street. He is the co-author of two e-books
        focusing on the 2012 presidential campaign, Politico Playbook 2012: The Right Fights Back
        and Inside the Circus: Romney, Santorum and the GOP Race.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="andrew_gillum_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session Four</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        A champion for everyday people, Andrew Gillum inspired millions across Florida and the nation
        in 2018. He surged past four better-funded primary candidates to a history-making victory as
        the Florida Democratic Party\'s first African-American nominee for governor.
        <p>
        A lifelong public servant, Andrew Gillum is recognized across Florida and the nation as a
        bold and inspirational leader. The former Mayor of Tallahassee and 2018 Florida Democratic
        gubernatorial nominee, Gillum brought Floridians together in pursuit of fundamental human
        rights — the right to a well-paying job; the right to a good education; the right to quality
        health care; the right not to live in fear of gun violence in our schools or our streets.
        The only Democratic candidate for governor in Florida this century who was not a millionaire,
        he won the hearts and minds of millions.
        <p>
        Above all, Andrew Gillum shows us what fearless leadership looks like.
        <p>
        Gillum\’s passion to fight for everyday people comes from his own life\’s journey. The son
        of a school bus driver and a construction worker, Andrew Gillum knows what it\'s like for a
        family to struggle, financially, and to have to choose between paying the water bill or the
        heating bill. The first in his family to graduate from high school and college, he knows
        first-hand how strong values, schools, and community can set an individual on a different course.
        <p>
        More than two million new midterm voters turned out in Florida in 2018 — shattering all
        records. The movement Mayor Gillum inspired is, without a doubt, responsible.
        <p>
        Andrew Gillum\’s efforts to help lift his fellow Floridians stretch back more than 15 years.
        Elected to the Tallahassee City Commission at age 23, he is youngest person elected in the
        city\’s history. At age 21, while still a student at Florida A&M University, he led a
        thousand students to protest Gov. Jeb Bush\'s attempt to end affirmative action. As a City
        Commissioner, he championed restorative justice programs to rehabilitate and educate offenders.
        He also created public-private partnerships to secure funding for computers and internet
        access for middle school students. As Mayor, Gillum spearheaded the construction of a
        20-megawatt solar farm, giving thousands of Tallahassee residents the ability to rely on
        clean, renewable energy for the first time. Recognizing Mayor Gillum\’s commitment to
        innovation and technology, President Obama named Tallahassee one of just 50 TechHire cities
        in the nation.
        <p>
        Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. once said, “Life\’s most persistent and urgent question is,
        \'What are you doing for others?\’” Andrew Gillum hears that call every day. And every day he
        works to answer it, dedicating his time, his talent, and his limitless passion into lifting
        up his fellow Americans.
        <p>
        Following his historic run for governor, Andrew Gillum was honored as one of the EBONY Power
        100 and named a 2019 Resident Fellow at the Institute of Politics (IOP) at Harvard Kennedy
        School. In January of 2019, Gillum joined CNN as a Political Commentator. Gillum resides in
        Tallahassee, Florida, with his wife, R. Jai, and their three children — Jackson, Caroline
        and Davis.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="donna_brazille_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session Three</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        Veteran political strategist Donna Brazile is the former interim chair of the Democratic
        National Committee (DNC), the author of the New York Times bestseller Hacks: The Inside
        Story of the Break-ins and Breakdowns That Put Donald Trump in the White House and the
        2004 best-selling memoir Cooking with Grease: Stirring the Pots in American Politics. She
        is a co-author of For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Politics, which won the 2019 NAACP
        Image Award for Outstanding Literary Work, Nonfiction.
        <p>
        Ms. Brazile has devoted her life to working for progressive change, responsible governance,
        and the advancement of all people in a society that is fair and equitable.  Brazile first
        got invovled in politics at the age of nine when she worked to elect a City Council
        candidate who had promised to build a playground in her neighborhood; the candidate won, the
        playground was built, and a lifelong passion for political progress was ignited.  Brazile
        has worked on every major presidential campaign since 1976 and in 2000 Ms. Brazile became the
        first African American woman to serve as the manager of a major party presidential campaign,
        running the campaign of former Vice President Al Gore.
        <p>
        Ms. Brazile loves working with young people, encouraging them to vote, to run for office, and
        to work within the system to strengthen it.  She has lectured at over 200 colleges and
        universities across the country on such topics as "Inspiring Civility in American Politics,"
        "Race Relations in the Age of Obama," "Why Diversity Matters," and "Women in American Politics."
        In 2013, Ms. Brazile was appointed by President Obama to serve on the J. William Fulbright
        Foreign Scholarship Board. She is also the proud recipient of more than ten honorary doctorate
        degrees from major colleges and universities, including her alma mater Louisiana State
        University. In October 2017, Ms. Brazile was the recipient of the W.E.B Du Bois Medal,
        Harvard\’s highest honor in African American studies.  Brazile has served as an adjunct
        professor at Georgetown University since 2002 and spent the fall of 2017 serving as a Joan
        Shorenstein fellow in Media, Politics and Public Policy at the Harvard Kennedy School.
        Howard University has appointed Ms. Brazile as the Gwendolyn S. and Colbert I. King Endowed
        Chair in Public Policy for two consecutive academic years.  In this capacity, she is
        responsible for developing and hosting a lecture series to engage the Howard community on
        several subjects, including politics, voting, criminal justice reform and civility.
        <p>
        O, The Oprah Magazine, chose Ms. Brazile as one of its 20 “remarkable visionaries” for the
        magazine\’s first-ever O Power List. In addition, she was named among the 100 Most Powerful
        Women by Washingtonian magazine, Top 50 Women in America by Essence magazine, and received
        the Congressional Black Caucus Foundation\’s highest award for political achievement. In
        2016, Ms. Brazile was awarded Wonk of the Year from the Kennedy Political Union at American
        University.  In March 2018, Black Enterprise awarded Ms. Brazile with the Barbara Graves
        Legacy Award.
        <p>
        Ms. Brazile has worked passionately on behalf of her beloved hometown of New Orleans. In the
        aftermath of the two catastrophic hurricanes that devastated the Gulf region, Ms. Brazile
        was appointed by former Governor Kathleen Blanco to serve on the Louisiana Recovery Board to
        work for the rebuilding of the state and to advocate for the Gulf recovery on the national
        stage. Ms. Brazile was also appointed by New Orleans Mayor Mitch Landrieu to serve on the
        Tricentennial Commission.
        <p>
        Ms. Brazile is a contributor to Fox News and was formerly a contributor to ABC News and CNN.
        Ms. Brazile was the recipient of a Daytime Emmy Award for Outstanding Daytime Program,
        Good Morning America (2016-2017) in connection with her work with ABC.  She has also been a
        syndicated newspaper columnist for Universal U\’Click and a prolific writer with articles
        appearing in nearly every major newspaper in the nation. She moonlights as an actress and is
        especially honored to have made three cameo appearances on CBS\’s The Good Wife, and two
        cameo appearances on Netflix\’s series House of Cards. She most recently appeared on BET\'s
        Being Mary Jane. Ask her and she\’ll tell you that acting, after all, is the key to success
        in politics.
        <p>
        Ms. Brazile is the founder and director of Brazile & Associates LLC, a general consulting,
        grassroots advocacy, and training firm based in Washington, DC.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="cameron_kasky_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session Three</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        On February 14, 2018, the lives of the students of Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School were
        forever changed when a lone gunman committed the deadliest high school shooting in United
        States history, killing 17 students and staff members and injuring 17 more. In the wake of
        the tragedy, Cameron Kasky and his fellow classmates recognized that they would not be the
        last Americans to have the worlds shattered, and that the gun violence epidemic was an issue
        of national safety. From that day forward, Kasky and other MSD students have implored legislators
        and citizens alike to answer the call to protect our nation\’s children. In an interview
        with Anderson Cooper, he bluntly stated that "my generation won\'t stand for this.”
        <p>
        In the days following the shooting, Kasky and several of the other survivors founded the
        #NeverAgain gun-control movement. They subsequently organized March For Our Lives, which
        would become one of the largest public demonstrations in American history with over 1 million
        people filling the streets of Washington, D.C. He and his cadre of classmates have traveled
        to over 70 cities in more than 20 states around the country on the “Road to Change” tour to
        advocate for gun control and promote youth engagement in political activism. Kasky has made
        regular appearances across several media outlets, using his social media channels to keep
        the issue of gun control in the national conversation and share the life of a young American
        activist standing tall in the face of fear.
        <p>
        A former student of Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School in Parkland, Florida, Cameron Kasky
        couples lessons from the classroom with real world experiences in civics, politics and media.
        The tragic Parkland shooting changed the trajectory of Cameron\’s life from talented student
        to nationally-recognized activist. His hopeful response in the face of national tragedy has
        made him a voice for his generation, issuing a wake up call to those in positions of authority.
        It catapulted him onto the national political stage, where he speaks to all who will listen
        about the mechanisms of change and the tools of social justice.
        <p>
        Topping Fast Company\’s list of the 100 Most Creative People for 2018, Kasky has appeared
        across multiple media outlets, including CNN, Fox News, The New Yorker, and TIME Magazine,
        where he and several other MSD students appeared on the March 2018 cover as part of a story
        entitled “The School Shooting Generation Has Had Enough.” He also submitted an Op-Ed for CNN,
        describing the events of the massacre and his reaction to it.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="errin_haines_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Politics & Media Panel</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Keller Theater - Lenfest</b>
        <p>
        Errin Haines is editor-at-large at The 19th, a nonprofit newsroom covering politics and
        centering women. Haines is an award-winning journalist whose previous experience includes
        reporting at The Associated Press, The Washington Post, The Orlando Sentinel and The Los
        Angeles Times.
        <p>
        Currently, Errin is focused on covering the intersections of race, gender and the 2020
        election. Her insightful reporting has focused on themes including the black electorate, the
        diversity of the 2020 Democratic field and how race and gender are playing out on the campaign
        trail. She is a frequent commentator on the election, appearing on news outlets such as CNN,
        MSNBC, CBS and NPR.
        <p>
        Errin\’s political coverage was also the topic of her Fall 2019 Ferris professorship at
        Princeton University, where she taught a class on the crucial role of black women in the
        2020 election. She is an Atlanta native and based in Philadelphia.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="joe_donnelly_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Session one</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Duchossois Tennis Center</b>
        <p>
        Joe Donnelly served on Capitol Hill for 12 years, including one term as U.S. Senator and
        three terms as a U.S. Representative. Joe advises clients in the financial services, defense
        and health care industries on a host of public policy and government relations issues.
        <p>
        While serving in the Senate, Joe served on a number of committees, including the Banking,
        Housing, and Urban Affairs Committee, where he was the Ranking Member of the National Security
        and International Trade and Finance Subcommittee; the Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition and
        Forestry, where he was the Ranking Member of the Commodities, Markets, Trade and Risk Management
        Subcommittee; and the Armed Services Committee, where he was the Ranking Member of the Strategic
        Forces Subcomitteee. He also served on the Special Committee on Aging.
        <p>
        His House tenure included service on the Financial Services and Veterans\’ Affairs committees.
        He was the Ranking Member on the Veterans\’ Affairs subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="jim_acosta_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Politics & Media Panel</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Keller Theater - Lenfest</b>
        <p>
        Jim Acosta is CNN chief White House correspondent, currently covering the Trump administration
        nd previously covered the Obama administration from the White House and around the world. He
        regularly covers presidential press conferences, visits by heads of states, and issues impacting
        the Executive Branch of the federal government. In addition, Acosta reported from the 2016
        campaign trail following Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump.
        <p>
        On June 11, 2019, HarperCollins released The Enemy of The People, an explosive, first-hand
        account of the dangers Acosta has faced reporting on the current White House while fighting
        on the front lines in President Trump\’s war on truth. In Mr. Trump\’s campaign against what
        he calls “Fake News,” the CNN Chief White House Correspondent is public enemy number one.
        Acosta presents a revealing examina- tion of bureaucratic dysfunction, deception, and the
        unprecedented threat the rhetoric Mr. Trump is directing poses to our democracy. When the
        leader of the free world incites hate and violence, Acosta doesn\’t back down, urging his
        fellow citizens to do the same.
        <p>
        Acosta is based in the network\'s Washington, D.C., bureau and serves as a substitute anchor
        for the network across a variety of CNN programs. Previously, Acosta was national political
        correspondent throughout CNN\'s \'America\'s Choice 2012\' election coverage, embedded with
        the Romney presidential campaign as the lead correspondent. He traveled with the GOP
        presidential candidate to key battle- ground states and to the U.K., Israel, and Poland,
        covering the latest campaign developments. Acosta sat down with Mitt Romney for two one-on-one
        interviews, breaking several political stories and presidential debate coverage. In addition,
        he covered both of President Barack Obama\'s inaugurations and contributed to the network\'s
        mid-term election coverage.
        <p>
        In 2009, when the Obama administration lifted some restrictions on American travel to Cuba,
        Acosta reported from Havana, Cuba, on the effects of the policy change and on the post-Cold
        War relationship of the United States and Cuba. During the 2008 presidential election, Acosta
        covered the campaigns of then-Sen. Hillary Clinton, Sen. John McCain and then-Sen. Barack Obama,
        frequently contributing as co-anchor on CNN\'s weekend political program, Ballot Bowl. During
        his time with CNN, Acosta has covered several breaking news stories, including the tragedy at
        Virginia Tech and the Gulf Coast during the oil spill crisis.
        <p>
        Before joining CNN in March 2007, Acosta was a CBS News correspondent since February 2003.
        Origi- nally based in New York, he later relocated to the CBS bureau in Atlanta. He contributed
        primarily to the CBS Evening News and has covered stories including the Iraq war from Baghdad,
        the 2004 presidential campaign of then-Sen. John Kerry, Hurricane Katrina, and the blackout
        of 2003 that impacted major cities in the Northeast U.S.
        <p>
        Previously, he was a correspondent for CBS Newspath, the network\'s 24-hour news service,
        from 2001-2003 and was based in Dallas and Chicago during that time. Acosta covered the
        Pennsylvania miner rescue, the Washington, D.C.-area sniper story and the Sept. 11 terrorist
        attacks, among other stories.
        <p>
        Prior to CBS Newspath, he was a reporter and substitute anchor for WBBM-TV, the CBS-owned
        station in Chicago from 2000 to 2001; a reporter for KTVT-TV, the CBS-owned station in Dallas,
        from 1998 to 2000 and a reporter and substitute anchor for WBIR-TV in Knoxville, Tenn., from
        1995 to 1998. He began his journalism career with WMAL-AM radio in Washington, before making
        the transition to television.
        <p>
        Acosta graduated cum laude from James Madison University with a bachelor\'s degree in mass
        communications and a minor in political science.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="bill_roberts_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date: Politics & Media Panel</b>
        <p>
            <b>Location: Keller Theater - Lenfest</b>
        <p>
        William Roberts is a senior producer for Al Jazeera in Washington, DC, and covered the
        impeachment of President Trump for the global news organization\’s website. Roberts is
        veteran Washington journalist who has written about national politics since 1994 for
        Knight-Ridder, The Economist Group, Bloomberg and Al Jazeera. He was in the US Capitol on
        September 11, 2001 for Bloomberg and covered the decisions that followed in Congress, the
        White House and the Pentagon during the presidency of George W. Bush. Prior to covering
        Washington, he was an award-winning business journalist for American City Business Journals
        in Philadelphia and New York for ten years. He is a 1983 graduate of Washington and Lee
        University with a BA in Journalism. He lives in Alexandria, Va.
        ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="parade_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date:</b> Feb. 14, 2020
        <p>
        <b>Time:</b> 9:00-10:30 AM
        <p>
        <b>Location:</b> Main Street - Downtown (Ticket Required)
        <p>
        Schedule:
        <p>
        Mock Convention state delegations line up along Main Street with floats decorated to mirror
        their state and decked out to match their delegation\’s energy. Past parades have featured
        live elephants and hot tubs, so keep an eye out for this year\'s excitement!
        <p>
        Explore the parade route in the general information section so you don’t miss a second of
        the fun.
        ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="session1_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date:</b> Feb. 14, 2020
        <p>
        <b>Time:</b> 1:30-4:00 PM
        <p>
        <b>Location:</b> Duchossois Tennis Center (Ticket Required)
        <p>
        Schedule:
        <p>
        <b>DOORS OPEN:</b> 12:30 PM
        <p>
        <b>SESSION START:</b> 1:30 PM
        <p>
        Join us for the opening of Convention Weekend 2020. We will be voting in the rules and welcome
        our first speakers to the stage, including Joe Donnelly and Symone Sanders.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER ONE: JOE DONNELLY</b>
        <p>
        Joe Donnelly served on Capitol Hill for 12 years, including one term as a U.S. Senator and
        three terms as a U.S. Representative. While in the Senate, Donnelly served on a number of
        committees, including the Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs Committee. He also served on
        the Special Committee on Aging.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER TWO: SYMONE SANDERS</b>
        <p>
        A champion for women, Symone D. Sanders is a strategist, communications consultant, and CNN
        political commentator. She also served as a Spring 2018 Resident Fellow at Harvard\’s
        Institute of Politics at the Kennedy School. Symone rose to prominence during her tenure as
        the National Press Secretary for U.S. Senator Bernie Sanders’ 2016 presidential campaign.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="session2_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date:</b> Feb. 14, 2020
        <p>
        <b>Time:</b> 6:00-9:00 PM
        <p>
        <b>Location:</b> Duchossois Tennis Center (Ticket Required)
        <p>
        Schedule:
        <p>
        <b>DOORS OPEN:</b> 5:00 PM
        <p>
        <b>SESSION START:</b> 6:00 PM
        <p>
        Session two re-opens the Convention and welcomes more exciting speakers to the stage,as well
        as student features.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER ONE: NADINE STROSSEN</b>
        <p>
        Nadine Strossen was the first female president of the American Civil Liberties Union and is
        a lead-ing expert in constitutional law and human rights. A frequent media commentator, she
        has been published widely in both academic and general interest publications. Her 2018 book,
        HATE: Why We Should Resist it With Free Speech, Not Censorship, has earned praise from
        ideologically diverse experts.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER TWO: PATTI SOLIS DOYLE</b>
        <p>
        Patti Solis Doyle is a nationally recognized political organizer, campaign strategist and
        CNN political commentator. She speaks regularly on the rise of women and minorities in
        politics, presidential campaigns and issues affecting Hispanic Americans.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="session3_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Date:</b> Feb. 15, 2020
        <p>
        <b>Time:</b> 10:00-1:00 PM
        <p>
        <b>Location:</b> Duchossois Tennis Center (Ticket Required)
        <p>
        Schedule:
        <p>
        <b>DOORS OPEN:</b> 9:00 AM
        <p>
        <b>SESSION START:</b> 10:00 AM
        <p>
        The start to the final day of Convention Weekend kicks off with a message from our General
        Chair and concludes with more engaging speakers.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER ONE DONNA BRAZILE</b>
        <p>
        Veteran political strategist Donna Brazile is the former interim Chair of the Democratic
        National Committee (DNC). She has devoted her life to working for progressive change,
        responsible governance, and the advancement of all people in a society that is fair and equitable.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER TWO CAMERON KASKY</b>
        <p>
        Cameron Kasky is the co-founder of March For Our Lives and a survivor of the deadliest high
        school shooting in United States\’ history. His hopeful response in the face of national
        tragedy has made him a voice for his generation, issuing a wakeup call to those in positions
        of authority. It catapulted him onto the national political stage, where he speaks to all
        who will listen about the mechanisms of change and the tools of social justice.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER THREE TREVOR NOAH</b>
        <p>
        Trevor Noah is the new voice of American politics. An award-winning comedian, host of
        “The Daily Show,” and insightful political commentator, Noah has a discerning voice on the
        2020 stage. In April 2018, Noah launched The Trevor Noah Foundation, a youth development
        initiative that enhances youth preparedness for higher education and entry into the workforce.
        ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="session4_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
         <b>Date:</b> Feb. 15, 2020
        <p>
        <b>Time:</b> 3:00-7:00 PM
        <p>
        <b>Location:</b> Duchossois Tennis Center (Ticket Required)
        <p>
        Schedule:
        <p>
        <b>DOORS OPEN:</b> 2:00 PM
        <p>
        <b>SESSION START:</b> 3:00 PM
        <p>
        The final session of Convention Weekend features the roll call vote, a final address from
        Andrew Gillum, and the Convention\’s prediction for the Democratic nominee. Join us for the
        exciting conclusion to four years of research and for the most accurate predictive convention
        in the country.
        <p>
        <b>SPEAKER ONE ANDREW GILLUM</b>
        <p>
        A champion for everyday people, Andrew Gillum inspired millions across Florida and the nation
        in 2018. He surged past four higher-polling primary candidates to a victory as the Florida
        Democratic Party\’s first African-American nominee for governor. A lifelong public servant,
        Andrew Gillum is recognized across Florida and the nation as a bold and inspirational leader.
        In January of 2019, Gillum joined CNN as a Political Commentator.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="politics_in_media_blurb">
        <![CDATA[
         <b>Date:</b> Feb. 13, 2020
        <p>
        <b>Time:</b> 7:00-8:30 PM
        <p>
        <b>Location:</b> Keller Theater - Lenfest (Ticket Required)
        <p>
        Schedule:
        <p>
        Mock Con 2020 is proud to present the Politics & Media Panel featuring leaders in the field
        of Political Media, Journalism, and Communications as they talk about the role of the media
        in the 2020 Presidential election. This event marks the beginning of the four-day process
        that is the Washington & Lee Mock Convention.
        <p>
        Jim Acosta is CNN chief White House correspondent, currently covering the Trump administration
        and previously covered the Obama administration from the White House and around the world.
        He regularly covers presidential press conferences, visits by heads of states, and issues
        impacting the Executive Branch of the federal government. In addition, Acosta reported from
        the 2016 campaign trail following Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump.
        <p>
        Tara McGowan is the Founder and CEO of progressive group ACRONYM, which recently launched a
        $75 million digital effort to counter Trump online. A longtime Democratic strategist, Tara
        McGowan has quickly become the leading voice on digital politics on the Left. She\’s
        regularly featured in major print outlets, and she has spoken about the 2020 digital race
        for the White House with on NPR and CNN.
        <p>
        Mike Allen is one of Washington\’s most influential and well-connected journalists. He is
        the co-founder and executive editor of Axios, a company delivering news and insights on
        politics, business, media, and tech. The company specializes in high-quality news and
        analysis easily shared among the country\’s influential readers and across social platforms.
        In addition to starting Axios, Allen was a co-founder at POLITICO, the media company that
        upended and revolutionized political and policy journalism.
        <p>
        Errin Haines is editor-at-large at The 19th, a nonprofit newsroom covering politics and
        centering on women. Haines is an award-winning journalist whose previous experience includes
        reporting at The Associated Press, The Washington Post, The Orlando Sentinel and The Los
        Angeles Times. Currently, Errin is focused on covering the intersections of race, gender and
        the 2020 election. She is a frequent commentator on the election, appearing on news outlets
        such as CNN, MSNBC, CBS and NPR.
        <p>
        William Roberts is a senior producer for Al Jazeera in Washington, DC, and covered the
        impeachment of President Trump for the global news organization. Roberts is a veteran journalist
        who has written about national politics since 1994 and covered Congress, the White House and
         the Pentagon. He is a 1983 graduate of W&L with a BA in Journalism.
        ]]>
    </string>


</resources>

